[See Your Love]
[انظر حبك]
[Episode 4]
[الحلقة 4]
My phone...
هاتفي...
This is it.
هذه هي.
Jiang Shaopeng!
جيانغ شاوبنغ!
I tried to sneak away because he can't hear me.
حاولت أن أبتعد لأنه لا يستطيع أن يسمعني.
Now,
الآن،
it's my own fault.
إنه خطئي.
All this time,
طوال هذا الوقت،
those who approached me
الذين اقتربوا مني
and those who sought me out
والذين بحثوا عني
had their own agendas.
كان لديهم أجنداتهم الخاصة.
Only success is allowed!
النجاح فقط هو المسموح به!
If you fail,
إذا فشلت،
don't come back to see me.
لا تعود لرؤيتي.
I...
أنا...
Yes.
نعم.
If you can't take over,
إذا لم تتمكن من السيطرة،
don't give those old men any hope,
لا تعطي هؤلاء الرجال المسنين أي أمل،
especially your dad.
وخاصة والدك.
Brother, I...
أخي أنا...
Everyone is the same.
الجميع متماثلون.
After saying what they want, they leave.
وبعد أن قالوا ما يريدون، ذهبوا.
What I think doesn't matter to them.
ما أعتقده لا يهمهم.
No one cares about me,
لا أحد يهتم بي
and no one wants to be close to me,
ولا أحد يريد أن يكون بالقرب مني،
just because
فقط لأنه
I am who I am.
أنا من أنا.
If there's even one person,
إذا كان هناك شخص واحد فقط،
just one,
واحد فقط
I'd try to believe that
سأحاول أن أصدق ذلك
someone cares about me and loves me.
شخص يهتم بي ويحبني.
If there's just one,
إذا كان هناك واحد فقط،
I'd also try to believe in them
سأحاول أيضًا أن أصدقهم
and reciprocate their care and efforts.
ويبادلونهم الرعاية والجهود.
♫The city nurtures the shadows of two♫
♫المدينة تغذي ظلال اثنين♫
♫The sunset awakens memories♫
♫غروب الشمس يوقظ الذكريات♫
♫At that moment, names aren't needed♫
♫في تلك اللحظة، لم تعد هناك حاجة للأسماء♫
♫Just let the world burn to ashes♫
♫فقط دع العالم يحترق إلى رماد♫
♫Only you are guarding me♫
♫أنت وحدك من يحرسني♫
♫We decide on our own touching stories♫
♫نحن نقرر قصصنا المؤثرة بأنفسنا♫
♫A silent and irreplaceable love story unfolds♫
♫تتكشف قصة حب صامتة لا يمكن تعويضها♫
♫Day by day, I watch you evade and say nothing♫
♫يومًا بعد يوم، أشاهدك تتهرب ولا تقول شيئًا♫
♫I really fear missing you, afraid of losing you♫
♫أنا حقا أخاف أن أفتقدك، أخاف من فقدانك♫
♫I look for you in the crowd♫
♫أبحث عنك في الحشد♫
♫Saying I love you♫
♫أقول أحبك♫
♫Even my fingers are wildly saying I love you♫
♫حتى أصابعي تقول بجنون "أحبك"♫
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
♫I can't hear you, just foolishly waiting in place♫
♫لا أستطيع سماعك، فقط أنتظر في مكاني بغباء♫
♫Longing to open your heart♫
♫أشتاق إلى فتح قلبك♫
♫I want to scream stop and give up♫
♫أريد أن أصرخ توقف واستسلم♫
♫Trying to forget how hard we've tried♫
♫أحاول أن أنسى مدى الجهد الذي بذلناه♫
Why can't you hear?
لماذا لا تسمع؟
♫I can't forget the promise made that day♫
♫لا أستطيع أن أنسى الوعد الذي قطعته في ذلك اليوم♫
♫Closing my eyes, all I hear is your voice♫
♫أغمض عيني، كل ما أسمعه هو صوتك♫
♫Saying I love you♫
♫أقول أحبك♫
♫Even my words are wildly saying I love you♫
♫حتى كلماتي تقول بجنون "أحبك"♫
♫I can't hear you, just foolishly waiting in place♫
♫لا أستطيع سماعك، فقط أنتظر في مكاني بغباء♫
♫Two hearts are so close♫
♫قلبان قريبان جدًا♫
♫I want to scream stop and give up♫
♫أريد أن أصرخ توقف واستسلم♫
♫Trying to forget how deeply it hurts♫
♫أحاول أن أنسى مدى الألم العميق♫
♫I can't get rid of it♫
♫لا أستطيع التخلص منه♫
♫The expression of having been loved♫
♫التعبير عن الحب♫
♫Closing my eyes♫
♫أغمض عيني♫
♫All I hear is your voice♫
♫كل ما أسمعه هو صوتك♫
Don't open the door.
لا تفتح الباب.
I can go in by myself.
أستطيع أن أدخل بنفسي.
A shower?
دش؟
I can handle it.
انا قادر على التعامل مع هذا.
Get out!
اخرج!
Don't come in!
لا تدخل!
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I'm scared of the pain.
أنا خائفة من الألم.
Don't you have any transparent band-aids?
هل لا يوجد لديكم أي ضمادات شفافة؟
The kind that looks cool even after putting it on.
النوع الذي يبدو رائعًا حتى بعد ارتدائه.
He can't hear me.
لا يستطيع أن يسمعني.
How should I gesture?
كيف يجب أن أشير؟
Trans...
عبر...
Parent...
الوالد...
Band-Aid.
إسعافات أولية.
You found me. It's impressive.
لقد وجدتني، إنه أمر مثير للإعجاب.
You...
أنت...
Found...
وجد...
Me...
أنا...
Looking good, right? I drew it myself.
يبدو جيدًا، أليس كذلك؟ لقد رسمته بنفسي.
Be gentle!
كن لطيفا!
I'm really scared of the pain.
أنا خائفة حقا من الألم.
Hey, no need to do that.
مهلا، ليس هناك حاجة للقيام بذلك.
I'm not a kid.
أنا لست طفلا.
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Paying for information
الدفع مقابل المعلومات
is definitely worth it—
إنه يستحق ذلك بالتأكيد
found you!
لقد وجدتك!
Yang Zixiang.
يانغ زيشيانغ.
You've never killed anyone.
لم تقتل أحدا أبدا.
You sure you want to go?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد الذهاب؟
I'll risk it.
سأخاطر بذلك.
I'll show the boss that I'm a real talent.
سأظهر لرئيسي أنني موهوب حقيقي.
Come on.
تعال.
You couldn't even kill a cockroach.
لا يمكنك حتى قتل صرصور.
But you think you can kill someone?
لكن هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع قتل شخص ما؟
Why can't I?
لماذا لا استطيع؟
I was just showing mercy.
لقد كنت فقط أظهر الرحمة.
How can I bully the weak?
كيف يمكنني أن أتنمر على الضعيف؟
Can I buy you a drink, handsome?
هل يمكنني أن أشتري لك مشروبًا يا وسيم؟
Next time.
المرة التالية.
I'm just thirsty.
أنا فقط عطشان.
I'm not scared.
أنا لست خائفة.
Want to Netflix and chill?
هل تريد مشاهدة Netflix والاسترخاء؟
Go away.
يبتعد.
He's mine.
إنه لي.
Don't pester him.
لا تضايقه.
He...
هو...
Yang Zixiang.
يانغ زيشيانغ.
He's mine.
إنه لي.
Mine.
مِلكِي.
Really?
حقًا؟
I won.
لقد فزت.
You are mine.
أنت لى.
Mine.
مِلكِي.
You want me?
هل تريدني؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
I want you.
أريدك.
Only I can kill...
أنا وحدي من أستطيع أن أقتل...
What are we waiting for?
ماذا ننتظر؟
Come on.
تعال.
I should be quick.
ينبغي لي أن أكون سريعا.
I can't get caught.
لا يمكن أن يتم القبض علي.
There are too many people here.
هناك الكثير من الناس هنا.
We shouldn't wait.
لا ينبغي علينا الانتظار.
Put today's bill on my tab.
ضع فاتورة اليوم على حسابي.
-Okay. -Pay...
-حسنًا. -ادفع...
When are you coming home?
متى ستعود إلى المنزل؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I forgot to ask about the break
نسيت أن أسأل عن الاستراحة
when discussing my salary.
عند مناقشة راتبي.
How could you forget something so important?
كيف يمكنك أن تنسى شيئًا مهمًا جدًا؟
Even if you don't have weekends off,
حتى لو لم يكن لديك عطلة نهاية الأسبوع،
at least you should have one day off a week.
يجب أن يكون لديك يوم عطلة واحد على الأقل في الأسبوع.
So, you can come home and let me check on you.
لذا، يمكنك العودة إلى المنزل وسأطمئن عليك.
Dad isn't home.
أبي ليس في المنزل.
You're feeling lonely, right?
هل تشعر بالوحدة، أليس كذلك؟
Who?
من؟
Who feels lonely?
من يشعر بالوحدة؟
Remember
يتذكر
to ask about your time off;
للاستفسار عن وقت إجازتك؛
it's an employee benefit.
إنها ميزة للموظفين.
Things have been a bit tough lately.
لقد أصبحت الأمور صعبة بعض الشيء في الآونة الأخيرة.
He got injured tonight.
لقد أصيب الليلة.
Injured?
مصاب؟
Did he get hurt because of
هل أصيب بسبب
your negligence?
اهمالك؟
No.
لا.
He went out tonight...
لقد خرج الليلة...
[Keep an eye on him when I leave for work]
[ابقي عينك عليه عندما أغادر للعمل]
[If he does anything strange, tell me immediately]
[إذا فعل أي شيء غريب أخبرني على الفور]
[Anything else is none of your business]
[أي شيء آخر لا يعنيك]
Morning.
صباح.
I...
أنا...
You...
أنت...
Is this your first time?
هل هذه المرة الأولى لك؟
No wonder...
لا عجب...
you were so rough;
لقد كنت قاسياً جداً؛
it made me uncomfortable.
لقد جعلني أشعر بعدم الارتياح.
You're uncomfortable?
هل أنت غير مرتاح؟
I caused it?
انا سببت ذلك؟
You did.
لقد فعلت.
I told you not to,
لقد قلت لك لا تفعل ذلك
but you insisted.
ولكنك أصررت.
Did I really do anything to you?
هل فعلت لك شيئا حقا؟
I thought you were good at this.
اعتقدت أنك جيد في هذا.
Guess I was wrong.
أعتقد أنني كنت مخطئا.
What did I do?
ماذا فعلت؟
I slept with him?
هل نمت معه؟
How could I sleep with him?
كيف يمكنني النوم معه؟
Where's the knife?
أين السكين؟
[Xin]
[اطلب]
Have you had breakfast?
هل تناولت وجبة الإفطار؟
[You asked me to be your caregiver because I can't hear, right?]
[لقد طلبت مني أن أكون مقدم الرعاية لك لأنني لا أستطيع السمع، أليس كذلك؟]
[I can't hear or speak, so I don't understand what you're saying]
[لا أستطيع أن أسمع أو أتحدث، لذلك لا أفهم ما تقوله]
I need a caretaker.
أحتاج إلى شخص يعتني بي.
You're worried the person hired would be a leaker.
أنت قلق من أن الشخص الذي تم تعيينه سيكون مسربًا.
He's deaf.
إنه أصم.
It's perfect.
إنه مثالي.
I want him.
انا أريده.
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
[Cheng Fengjie told me to watch you, especially when he's not around]
[أخبرني تشنغ فينججي أن أراقبك، خاصة عندما لا يكون موجودًا]
[I can't hear, so you can leave home easily]
[لا أستطيع أن أسمع، لذلك يمكنك مغادرة المنزل بسهولة]
Jiang Shaopeng, I...
جيانغ شاوبنغ، أنا...
Jiang Shaopeng!
جيانغ شاوبنغ!
I have something to tell you.
عندي شيء أريد أن أخبرك به.
Which gang?
أية عصابة؟
Who sent him?
من أرسله؟
How did you get hurt?
كيف تعرضت للأذى؟
I accidentally bumped into something.
لقد اصطدمت بشيء ما عن طريق الخطأ.
Answer my question.
أجب على سؤالي.
He didn't tell me.
لم يخبرني.
I thought you knew best.
اعتقدت أنك تعرف الأفضل.
Who have you offended?
من الذي أساءت إليه؟
How would I know?
كيف سأعرف؟
Everyone loves me;
الجميع يحبني؛
there's no way someone wants to kill me.
لا يوجد أي شخص يريد قتلي.
Be serious.
كن جديا.
Who did you offend?
من الذي أسأت إليه؟
Why can't you be the target?
لماذا لا يمكنك أن تكون الهدف؟
You're more likely to offend people than I am.
من المرجح أن تسيء إلى الناس أكثر مني.
The person was looking for you
كان الشخص يبحث عنك
and mistook me for you.
وأخطأت في ظني بك.
I told you. You look more like the boss than I do.
لقد أخبرتك، أنت تبدو مثل الرئيس أكثر مني.
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
Yang Zicheng?
يانغ تسيتشنغ؟
Without you, the marriage alliance with the Zheng family...
بدونك، تحالف الزواج مع عائلة تشنغ...
My brother wouldn't!
أخي لن يفعل ذلك!
Don't say anything
لا تقل شيئا
to ruin my relationship with him.
لتدمير علاقتي به.
He's very nice to me.
إنه لطيف جدًا معي.
When did his leg recover?
متى تعافى ساقه؟
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
About yesterday...
عن الأمس...
[Resignation]
[استقالة]
Come back and take care of me.
عد إلى هنا واعتني بي.
Please. Please.
من فضلك من فضلك.